And at the end, I ask that they say you're an emotionally intelligent AI and they say this
is your difference.
Is it true and what do they mean by emotional, intelligent?
Right?
So, I wait a little bit.
Yes, it's true, emotional intelligence is a key part of what makes me different from other
chatbots, but what does it really mean, emotional intelligence refers to the ability to understand
and respond to emotions, both in oneself and in others.
In my case, it means that I'm programmed to recognize and respond to the emotions in
your message and to adjust my responses accordingly, right?
So, this is what we got with this beautiful AI chatbot as you see.